我最近读到在二战期间
I recently read that during World War Two,
约瑟夫·斯大林曾有一项研究计划
Joseph Stalin had a research program
为了制造超级士兵
to create supersoldiers
要让女人怀上大猩猩的孩子
by having women impregnated by gorillas.
太变态的滥用科学了
What a sick use of science.
只要孩子健康就没事啦
Hey, as long as the baby's healthy.
不知道斯大林有没想过使用其他动物
I wonder if Stalin considered any other animals.
河马是杀伤性最高的动物
Hippos are the deadliest creature.
半人半河马应该会是狠角色吧
A half-human, half-hippo soldier would be pretty badass.
但当它们饿饿的时候
Yes, but when they're hungry-hungry,
你用弹珠就能阻止它们了
you can stop them with marbles.
是的  制造跨族超级士兵的
Yeah, the correct animal
最佳选择是考拉
for interspecies supersolider is koala.
你可以做出一个超可爱  让人无法下手的军队
You would wind up with an army so cute it couldn't be attacked.
但半人半猫头鹰可以飞...
But half-man, half-owl could fly...
正解就是让人想抱的大扁鼻子士兵
The answer is cuddly soldiers with big flat noses.
下个话题
Moving on.
佩妮  新工作什么时候开始
So, Penny, when's the new job start?
下周一
Next Monday.
你找时间看了我给你的材料了吗
Did you get a chance to look over the materials I gave you?
还没  但我会看的
Uh, not yet, but I will.
很好  什么时候
Great. When?
我说了我会去看
I said I'll get to it.
我好像感觉到场面有些尴尬  是吧
I'm sensing awkwardness, am I right?
是的
Yes.
厉害
Swish.
我不想一直逼你
I don't want to be pushy,
但你之前从未接触过医药销售
but you've never done pharmaceutical sales before.
你可以用这段时间领先其他人啊
It seems like you could use this time to get a head start.
前几周都是在培训
Well, the first few weeks will be all training.
他们会教我一切需要了解的信息
They'll tell me everything I need to know.
但你想象一下  你去的时候已经对材料很熟
But imagine how impressed they'd be if you showed up
他们肯定会对你刮目相看
already familiar with the material.
所以是怎样  你想让我当老师的小马屁精吗
Okay, so what, you want me to be like a teacher's pet?
又没坏处
Couldn't hurt.
不知道啊
Mm, I don't know.
在座这里有谁
Who here has ever been hurt
因为当老师的马屁精被欺负过
because they were the teacher's pet?
感觉就像班上其他同学想要老师
It was like the rest of the class wanted Ms. McDonald
忘了有考试
to forget the quiz.
戴维斯小姐
Mrs. Davis.
你猜是谁
Guess who?
库伯博士
Dr. Cooper.
没错  干得好
That's right, good job.
你好
Hello.
你想见我吗
Uh, you wanted to see me?
是的  欢迎回来
Yes. Uh, welcome back.
谢谢
Thank you.
我想你想要再开始
I assume you'd like to reopen our dialogue
大学逼我继续研究弦理论的谈话是吗
about the university forcing me to continue with string theory?
你是指谈话过程只有
You mean the dialogue that went,
"拜托""不行"这两个词来回重复的那次吗
"Please?" "No." "Please?" "No." "Please?" "No."
没错
That's the one.
我记得上一次最后是你回的  所以...  拜托
I believe you went last, so, uh, please?
库伯博士  在你不在的时候  我们想出了
Dr. Cooper, while you were away, we came up with a solution
让你可以改变研究领域的方法了
that would allow you to change your field of study.
撅嘴逃跑真的管用啊
Pouting and running away actually worked.
不得不说  你可千万记得
Yeah, I must say, that may not be a lesson
不要再逼我干嘛了
you want to reinforce with me.
所以解决方式是什么
So, um, what is the solution?
目前大学给你的研究基金是
Currently, you're being paid under a grant
只能做特定领域研究的
to specifically research string theory.
如果我们将你升为初级教授
If we promote you to junior professor,
这样你就能
you'll be able to choose
想研究什么就研究什么
whatever field of research you'd like.
但如果我是教授  我就得带学生了
But if I'm a professor, then I'll have to teach a class.
没错
That is correct.
所以你的解决方法就是  给我升职  给我加薪
So your solution is to promote me and pay me more money
然后让我能把我的学识
so that I can impart my knowledge
传授给下一代的科学家们吗
to the next generation of scientists?
没错
Yes.
你们这帮人真变态
You people are sick.
准备好去吃午饭了吗
Hey. Ready to go to lunch?
再给我一分钟
Just give me a minute.
我在刺激海星的快感细胞
I'm stimulating the pleasure cells of this starfish.
等我关了就行了
I just need to turn it off.
如果你不关掉会怎么样
What happens if you don't?
那我就得边吃午饭
Then I have to sit through lunch
边想着这海星过得比我还"爽"
knowing this starfish is having a better day than I am.
伯纳黛特会在餐厅跟我们碰面吗
Is Bernadette meeting us at the restaurant?
不会  其实我没叫她
Uh, no. Actually, I didn't invite her.
为什么
How come?
自从她介绍了我这份工作
Well, ever since she helped me get this job,
她就一直不停地烦我
she won't stop bugging me.
她只想你能做好这份工作
Well, I think she just wants you to do well,
而且她也担心你会失败吧
and she's worried that you won't
因为你真是个超烂的服务员
'cause you were just a stunningly poor waitress.
才不是呢
That is not true.
我到现在都还在等两年前跟你点的玉米热狗呢
I'm still waiting on my mini corndogs from two years ago.
我跟你说了  很快会给你上
I told you, they'll be right out.
好吧  没有伯纳黛特
Okay, so no Bernadette.
那晚你也看见她那个样子啦  难道是我错吗
Well, you saw her the other night. Am I wrong?
没有啊  我只是...
No, I just...
我觉得这样说她有点不好
I feel kind of uncomfortable talking about her like this.
通常有人在背后说其他人坏话时
Usually when someone's being talked about behind their back,
都是说我的坏话  而且还当着我的面说
it's me and it's right in front of my face.
抱歉  我只是想躲开她一阵子
I-I'm sorry. I just need a little break from her.
我懂
I understand.
你知道吗  有些研究显示
You know, there is some research that indicates
分享对第三方的负面看法
that sharing negative attitudes about a third party
能够加深两个朋友之间的友谊吗
can be a powerful bonding force between two friends.
所以你是什么意思
So, what are you saying?
我的意思是  为了科学
I'm saying, in the spirit of science,
那个小婊砸到底有啥好不满的
what is that little skank's problem?
我一直想给
So, I've been trying to come up
我和艾米丽取一个可爱的情侣昵称
with a cute couple's nickname for me and Emily.
你觉得哪一个好
What do you like better--
艾米帕里
Emippali...
还是库萨帕米丽
or Koothrapemily?
为什么一定是你的姓和她的名的组合
Why is it your last name and her first name?
她姓斯威尼
Oh, well, her last name is Sweeney,
库萨帕威尼听起来不大对劲儿
and something just didn't seem right about Koothrapeeney.
跟人力资源部谈得怎么样了
Hey, how'd it go with human resources?
很糟糕
Awful.
虽然他们同意让我研究其他理论
Yeah, they're allowing me to move on from string theory,
但是他们升我当初级教授
but they made me a junior professor
这样我就必须给学生上课
and are requiring me to teach a class.
我不明白了  上课有什么不好
I don't understand. Why is it bad that you have to teach?
愚蠢的问题
What a stupid question.
学生们绝对会"喜欢"他
The kids are gonna love him.
我不敢相信我得浪费我的时间
I can't believe I have to waste my time
照顾一群研究生
babysitting a bunch of grad students
他们可能觉得暗物质就是尿片里的屎尿
who probably think dark matter is what's in their diapers.
没那么糟糕
This might not be that bad.
你喜欢指出别人的错误
Uh, you like telling people they're wrong.
错
Wrong!
我喜欢这么做  并不代表我会想整天这么做
Just because I enjoyed that one doesn't mean I always do.
你喜欢给别人打分
You enjoy giving people grades.
观点正确  但是非原创  B-
A valid point, but unoriginal-- B-minus.
你喜欢你自己的声音
And you love the sound of your own voice.
对  没错  我喜欢
Yeah, well, of course I do.
听听
Listen to it.
就像听到了融化的焦糖
It's like an earful of melted caramel.
最重要的是
Look, most importantly,
这样你才能继续研究暗物质
this will let you move on and study dark matter.
我有很多偶像倒是都曾给予过
It is true that many of my heroes have taken students
学生帮助[放在翅膀下]
under their wings:
费因曼  爱因斯坦  X教授
Feynman, Einstein, Professor X.
费因曼  美国著名物理学家
X教授  即查尔斯·塞维尔  X战警学校的校长及创办人
有趣的是
Humorously,
对于X教授来说
in the case of Professor X,
他的一些学生还真的有翅膀
some of his students actually had wings.
真有意思
That's rich.
等全班学生在期中考试挂科之后
I'll use that one to lighten the mood
我会用这个笑话来逗笑他们
after my entire class fails the midterm.
通过使用1.2摩尔的快感细胞刺激
Measuring starfish serotonin levels in response to
测量海星的血清素等级
one point two molar stimulation of pleasure cells.
你喜欢这样对吧
You like that, don't you?
没错  说我的名字
That's right, say my name.
-还好吗  -还行
- Hey, what's going on? - Not much.
等会儿要去喝一杯吗
You want to get a drink later?
就我俩
Just the two of us?
不叫佩妮吗
No Penny?
今晚不叫她  我对她有点失望
Not tonight. I'm a little frustrated with her.
因为你帮她找到工作
Because you got her the job and you think
你觉得她应该好好准备
she should be working harder to prepare for it?
原来不光是我  你也看到了
So it's not just me. You see it, too!
对  我也看到了
I do, I see it.
快把我逼疯了
It's driving me crazy.
今天下午  我在她的相册里看见
Just this afternoon, I saw on Instagram
她没有好好学习  还跑出去吃午餐
that instead of studying, she went out to lunch
还去做了美甲
and got a manicure.
太过分了
That's outrageous!
对啊
I know!
如果她做不好
If she doesn't do well,
也会坏了你的名声
th-this could reflect poorly on you.
是啊  她是不知道  还是不在乎
Exactly. Does she not realize it or does she not care?
我不知道
I don't know.
重要的是  我支持你
The important thing is I am here for you
所以我们可以一起鄙视这个讨厌的第三方
so we can mutually disparage this unpleasing third party.
我们来看看你的课上得怎么样了
Hey. We just wanted to see how your class was going.
学生呢
Where is everybody?
没有学生
There is no class.
你这么快就把所有人都送去校长办公室了吗
Did you send everyone to the principal's office already?
没人报名
No one signed up.
这不是你的错
Well, that's not your fault.
我打电话问学院秘书是怎么回事
I called the department secretary to see what happened.
显然  全校的人都认为我很讨厌
Apparently, I have a reputation for being obnoxious.
不会吧
What?
谢尔顿  真是抱歉
Hey, Sheldon, I'm sorry.
别  没事的
No, it's fine.
现在我可以全身心投入到暗物质的研究中了
Now I can devote all my time to dark matter.
你还给大家带了饼干
Aw, you brought cookies for everyone?
对  "无花果牛顿"饼干
Oh, yes. Fig Newtons.
我本来打算问他们  哪个科学家
I was going to ask them: which scientist both helped
既对微积分有贡献
to develop calculus
又有一款饼干以他命名
and had a famous cookie named after him?
等有人回答"牛顿"
And then after someone said "Newton,"
我就告诉他们错了
I was going to tell them they're wrong.
这个饼干是用马萨诸塞州的一个镇命名的
The cookies are named after a town in Massachusetts.
然后我再把饼干扔了
And then I'd throw the cookies away.
我来听你的课怎么样
Hey, what if I took your class?
你为什么这么做
Why would you do that?
-你为什么这么做  -你脑子出什么问题
- Yeah, why would you do that? - What's wrong with you?
我想拿到博士学位
I'm thinking about getting my doctorate,
他想要教课  正好啊
and he wants to teach-- why not?
霍华德
Oh, Howard.
感谢你的提议
I appreciate the gesture,
但这是研究生阶段的物理课程
but this is a graduate-level physics class.
我觉得你根本无法理解
I don't think you'd understand
我所讲的任何内容
a single thing I was talking about.
再问一遍为什么不能来  我有答案了
Ask why not again; I've got an answer.
谢尔顿  我的智商来听你的课绰绰有余了
Sheldon, I'm more than smart enough to take your class.
不可能
No.
真的
Yes.
在没有精确解的情况下
How would you determine the ground state
你如何确定量子系统的基态
of a quantum system with no exact solution?
我会任意猜测一个基态波函数  通过更改其参数
I would guess a wave-function and then vary its parameters
找出能量最低的量子态
until I found the lowest energy solution.
你知道怎么不查书也能求出
Do you know how to integrate X squared times E
x平方乘e到负x的积分
to the minus X, without looking it up?
我会用费曼的秘诀
I'd use Feynman's trick--
积分符号内取微分
differentiate under the integral sign.
不错嘛
Okay.
量子力学的正确诠释是什么
What is the correct interpretation of quantum mechanics?
每一种诠释对于每一次测量
Since every interpretation gives exactly the same answer
给出的答案都一样  所以它们同等正确
to every measurement, they are all equally correct.
但是我知道你支持的是多宇宙诠释
However, I know you believe in the Many Worlds Interpretation,
所以我会顺着你说  现在你觉得我够聪明了吗
so I'll say that. Now do you think I'm smart enough?
不
No.
拜托  你也许就比我
Oh, come on. You might've gone to school
多上了几年学  但是
for a couple more years than me, but guess what--
工程师和物理学家一样聪明
engineers are just as smart as physicists.
你把这话收回去
You take that back!
不
No.
和伯纳黛特喝了几杯后
So, after drinks with Bernadette,
我刚到家  佩妮就打来电话抱怨伯纳黛特
I get home, and Penny calls to complain about her.
我正和佩妮说着呢
And then while I'm talking to Penny,
伯纳黛特又发来短信
I get a text from Bernadette.
我正为霍华德准备教学计划呢
Wh... I'm trying to prepare my lesson plan for Howard.
你干嘛告诉我这些废话
Why are you telling me this?
因为虽然晚了15年
Because it's taken 15 years,
但高中生活终于开始精彩了
but high school is finally awesome!
虽然我爱她们俩
I love them both,
但现在我成了团体中心  我更爱这种感觉
but I'm in the center now, and I love that even more.
艾米  拜托  我正努力寻找
Amy, please. I am trying to figure out a way
一种用智力阉割我好友的方法
to intellectually emasculate a dear friend of mine.
-可人家...  -别烦我了
- But I'm just... - Not now.
注意你的态度  老弟
You better watch that attitude, buddy.
你女朋友现在可是校园红人呢
You're dating the popular girl now.
你还没睡啊
You're up late.
我在为沃罗威茨量身定制教学计划
Oh, I'm working on my lesson plan for Wolowitz.
保证他跟听天书一样
He is going to be so lost.
快看这部分内容
Look at this section over here.
连我都不懂是什么
Even I don't really understand it.
谢尔顿  你为什么要这么做
Sheldon, why are you doing this?
我是一名教师  莱纳德
I'm a teacher, Leonard.
这是我的工作
It's my job.
不  我是说
No, I-I mean,
你为什么要费尽周折
why are you going to so much trouble
来证明你比沃罗威茨聪明呢
to prove that you're smarter than Wolowitz?
完全不费劲  我高兴着呢
Oh, it's no trouble; it's actually a pleasure.
你知道我怎么想吗
You want to know what I think?
我觉得一想到某人可能和你一样聪明
I think the idea that someone could be as smart as you,
甚至比你聪明  你就怕得要死
or even smarter, scares the pants off you,
你接受不了这个事实
and you can't deal with it.
想法很有趣
Interesting point.
你是在暗示
Wh... You're suggesting
潜意识里我的情绪
that I have emotional issues below my consciousness
影响了我的行动
which drive my behavior,
导致我大肆打击任何
thus causing me to lash out at anything or anyone
威胁到我智商优势的人或事吗
that threatens my intellectual superiority.
你好好思考一下吧
Might be something to think about.
-莱纳德  -什么
- Leonard? - Yeah.
霍华德对花生过敏
Howard's allergic to peanuts.
我怎样才能用这个对付他
How can I use that against him?
既然大家都来齐了  我们可以上课了
Okay, now that everyone's here, we can begin.
上课之前我要说  我刚和莱纳德谈过了
Before we do, I just talked to Leonard.
如果你准备
And if you're gonna
刻意让这门课难到超乎常理
spend all your time trying to belittle me
以此来贬低我的智商的话
by making this class unnecessarily hard,
那我不上了
then I'm out.
但如果你真心想要
But if you're interested in making
做一个好老师
a sincere effort to be a good teacher,
那我也愿意给你个机会
then I'm willing to give this a shot.
这个提议很合理
I suppose that's a fair request.
我们俩都可以从这件事里受益
There's no reason we both can't benefit from this experience.
-好吧  -就这样
- Okay. - Okay.
那我们先上课
Well, then, uh, first things first.
你对最速降线问题熟悉吗
Um, are you familiar with the Brachistochrone problem?
-很熟悉  -很好
- I am. - Good.
那它和变分法之间的关系呢
And how it relates to the calculus of variations?
是一条翻转摆线
It's an inverted cycloid.
不错不错
Wonderful.
那么  你了解欧拉拉格朗日定理吗
Now, what about Euler-Lagrange theorems?
这我就有点小困惑了
That's where I'm a little fuzzy.
我就知道  好了
Ha! I knew it! All right.
在第一次考试前  我们需要大量补充这方面的知识
We have a lot of information to cover before your first test.
对了  考试就在8分钟之后
Which, by the way, is in eight minutes.
好消息是我的评分标准是曲线评分
The good news is I'm grading on a curve,
所以你卷子上肯定有个"C"
so you're pretty much guaranteed a C.
* 老子这辈子只想赢 *
* All I do is win, win, win *
* 无论如何 *
* No matter what *
你这是在干什么
What are you doing?
* 大家一起高举双手 *
* Everybody hands go up, up... *
* 保持别动 *
* And they stay there! *
你在干什么
What are you doing?
如果你要当个烂老师
If you're gonna be a crappy teacher,
那我就当个烂学生
then I'm gonna be a crappy student.
* 路达克里斯来唱副歌 *
* Ludacris going in on the verse *
* 我无所不胜  永不停止 *
*'Cause I never been defeated and I won't stop now..*
停下来
Will you stop it!
这是教室
This is a classroom.
不是《美国大舞台》  好了
This is not American Bandstand. Okay.
好了  我说到哪里呢
Now, where was I?
我看看
Let's see.
对了  就是这里
Oh, yes. Over here.
你
You...
你又在干什么
What are you doing now?
折一个吸管
Making a straw.
为什么
Why?
我就可以用口水球射你了
So I can shoot you with a spitball.
你不能这么做  我来告诉你为什么
You're not going to do that, and I'll tell you why.
这里是高等学府的课堂
This is an institution of higher learning,
我是你的教授
I am your professor,
你对待我的态度应该是...
and you're going to treat me with the prop...
你的口水吐进我的嘴里了
You shot your spit in my mouth!
考试会考这个吗
Is that gonna be on the test?
我想我没法再做到一次了
Because I don't think I can do that again.
好闺蜜
Hey, girlfriend.
可以来个那啥啥吗
Can I get a what what?
啥
What?
差不多了
Close enough.
我打来想问问你今晚有什么安排
Um, I was just calling to see what you were up tonight.
咱们可以去整整"自己动手做彩陶"
Thought maybe we could hit up Color Me Mine,
偷偷带进去一些葡萄酒  随便啦
maybe sneak in some Pinot Greej. Whatevs.
多谢了  但我要留在家
Uh, thanks, but I think I'm gonna stay in
学习伯纳黛特给我的资料
and go over the stuff Bernadette gave me.
哦  这样啊
Oh. Oh, I hear you.
好让唠叨鬼不再烦你对吧
Try and get that nag off your back, right?
你又不是单车
I mean, you're not a bicycle;
她凭什么这样"骑压"你
why's she riding you like that?
不  我想她只是想帮忙
No, I think she was just trying to help.
而且  我想做好这份工作
Plus, I really want to do well at this job. So...
那祝你好运  晚点打给我
Okay, good luck. And call me later,
如果你要抱怨她是个贱人什么的
you know, if you decide she's a bitch or something.
好闺蜜
Hey, girlfriend.
艾米
Hey, Amy.
今晚  你和我  "自己动手做彩陶"
Tonight. You, me, Color Me Mine.
也许带点葡萄酒进去  整个"自己动嘴喝彩酒"
Maybe we sneak in some pinot-- make it Color Me Wine.
听起来很好玩  但我答应了佩妮
That sounds fun, but I promised Penny
过去帮助她学习
I'd come by and help her study.
那只能祝你好运逮到她
Oh. Well, good luck getting her to do that.
她可能又出去修指甲了
She's probably off getting another manicure.
你记得她那次这样做吗
You remember when she did that?
记得吗
You remember?
我可能对她太严厉了
I was probably being too hard on her.
我们谈过了  没事了
We talked, we're good.
太好了
Oh. Great.
我为你们高兴
I'm happy for you guys.
你俩合不来时
You know, when the two of you aren't getting along,
我夹在中间  好难做人啊
it puts me in a really weird position.
不用担心  一切恢复正常了
Well, don't worry-- everything's back to normal.
你是指她表面上又跟你好了吗
You mean, like, where she's nice to your face?
明白了  拜
Okay got it. Bye.
好男友
Hey, boyfriend.
没时间说话  口水球
Can't talk. Spitball.
可能会死
Probably gonna die.
怎么样
Well?
谢尔顿  我发誓
Sheldon, I-I promise.
你的小舌没得性病
Your uvula does not have an STD.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
感觉没有以前那么纯洁了
It just doesn't feel as innocent as it used to.
你把我告到人事部去了吗
You reported me to human resources?
你亵渎了我口腔的圣洁
You violated the sanctity of my mouth.
我不上你的课了  希望你开心
Well, I dropped your class, so I hope you're happy.
我跟你说过  你不够聪明  不能上我的课
I told you you weren't smart enough to take it.
我够聪明了  谢尔顿
I'm smart enough, Sheldon.
问我一大堆
Asking me a bunch of questions
我不熟悉的课题的问题
about a topic I'm not familiar with
并不能证明什么
doesn't prove anything.
我也可以问你
I could do the same to you.
是吗  试试
Yeah... Try me.
好的
Okay.
你非常享受取笑工程学
You enjoy making fun of engineering so much;
那么你如何量化材料强度
how do you quantify the strength of materials?
杨氏模量
Young's modulus.
-对吗  -对
- Is that right? - Yeah.
你如何预防变压器中的涡流损耗
Okay, how do you prevent eddy currents in a transformer?
层压芯材
Laminate the core material.
拜托  问个难的
Come on, give him a hard one.
这就是难的
That was a hard one.
好吧
All right.
管直径如何决定流量
How does the flow rate in a pipe depend on its diameter?
你不知道  对吗
You don't know, do you?
怎么啦  聪明人
What's the matter, smart guy?
不知道泊肃叶定律了吧
Don't know Poiseuille's law?
谢天谢地出来了
Thank goodness I got it!
现在我不必再检查我的粪便了
Now I can quit checking my stool.
我们的壮阳药有些什么
Okay, what are the potential side effects
可能的副作用
for our erectile dysfunction drug?
头痛  头晕  恶心
Headaches, dizziness and nausea.
是的
Yes.
一个勃起的75岁老男人
Those are also the side effects
趴在你身上  你也会出现这些副作用
of having a 75-year-old man with an erection climb on top of you.
-要不要停下来  -不用  我可以继续
- Want to stop here? - Uh, no. I can keep going.
不必了  你能行的
Nah, you got this.
我们去喝一杯  我打给艾米
Let's go for a drink. I'll call Amy.
好的  她似乎今晚特别想出去玩
Okay, good. She seemed like she really wanted to go out tonight.
干嘛  妹子
Hey, girl.
下个问题  奖品是金手指黄油饼干
Okay, next question, for the Butterfinger:
银河年有多长
how long is a galactic year?
两亿五千万年
250 million years!
对了
Yes!
这个的奖品是吉百利蛋
Okay, this one is for a Cadbury Creme Egg.
复活节都没到呢
It's not even Easter time.
太疯狂了
This is crazy!
哪种阿基米德多面体有20个规则的三角面
Which Archimedean solid has 20 regular triangular faces,
30个四角面  12个五角面
30 square faces, 12 pentagonal faces,
60个顶点和120条边
60 vertices and 120 edges?
小斜方截半二十面体
The Rhombicosidodecahedron!
答对了
Yes!
我们太聪明了
We are so smart!
高中时为什么女生不喜欢咱们
Why didn't girls like us in high school?
因为我们呆滞怪异
Because we were awkward and weird
-而且运动无能  -又答对了
- and couldn't play sports! - Right again!